

Prakhar Tated Senior Systems Engineer

prakhartated@gmail.com

9424857401

BETUL, India

linkedin.com/in/prakhar-tated-28322111b

github.com/prakhartated

Solution oriented application developer always up for learning new web technologies and using my knowledge to its best use. Having 2+ years of experience in Frontend technologies like React JS, JavaScript, HTML, CSS, Bootstrap along with CMS like Sitecore and Kentico. Having hands-on experience in designing, developing and deploying solutions. Provided optimum solutions to client which helped them to meet the requirements. Quick learner and have ability to meet deadlines & work under pressure.

TECHNICAL SKILLS

HTML | CSS | JAVASCRIPT FrontEnd **CMS** SITECORE | KENTICO

Frameworks REACT JS Project JIRA | GITHUB | AZURE

Management

Language C# | JAVA | PHP **BackEnd** Node JS

Databases MySQL | pgAdmin

WORK EXPERIENCE

Senior Systems Engineer

Infosys

01/2022 - Present

- Elanco UK
- Knetico | JS | pgAdmin | Node JS | HTML | Bootstrap | CSS.
- Working as main UI developer for the team.
- Using Kentico CMS and Node JS for creating multiple forms and using pgAdmin for storing the result.
- Responsible for creating and using APIs.
- Worked on Admin Bypass security issues adding security to admin related details.

Systems Engineer

Infosys

10/2020 - 12/2021

- Molina Healthcare Project
- React | Bootstrap | HTML | CSS | JS | SITECORE | GITHUB | AZURE.
- Responsible for designing UI, various forms, API Binding, and content creation.
- Used Bootstrap for UI development used Formik forms and yup for validation.
- Used Sitecore for Content creation and updating & responsible for testing in Experience Editor for content changes.
- Responsible for deploying code on Azure pipelines.
- Responsible for binding API with RESTFUL services worked on MFA Functionality while updating critical information.

Systems Engineer Trainee

Infosvs

02/2020 - 09/2020

- Infosys Capstone Project
- React | MySQL | JS | Bootstrap.
- Created a online shopping portal including searching, selecting and saving of products to cart and buying them.
- Responsible for designing UI.
- Used Formik for creating forms and added yup validation.

HONOR AWARDS

Insta Award (01/2022)

Infosys

- For Support and deployment of project

Insta Award (11/2021)

Infosv.

 For providing beneficial solution and timely completion of Molina Project

ACHIEVEMENTS

3rd prize in modernization competition

PERSONAL PROJECTS

Online Shopping Portal (01/2019 - 03/2019)

- JAVA | HTML | CSS | Bootstrap | Gmail API | MySQL.
- Created an Online Shopping Portal through which customer can view a variety of products, search them, add them to cart and even purchase them.
- Used Java as base language and Gmail API as security check while logging in to a new device.
- Designed UI for the project and all the functionalities required for the successful execution of the project.

Psychology Blogging Portal (04/2019 - 06/2019)

- PHP | HTML | CSS | BOOTSTRAP | MySQL.
- Created a blogging portfolio website for a psychologist.
- Site included certain features as timeline and social media API to show all the required and relatable feeds to viewers.
- Responsible for creating an Admin section for creating and updating blogs and provided a database to hold all the entries.

EDUCATION

O Bachelor of Technology (Computer Science)

SBITM (RGPV University)

08/2015 - 06/2019 Betul